{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1106","name":"Music Hall Center","address":"350 Madison","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Music Hall Center","licenseNumber":"035181","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.04577,42.33702","geojson":{"id":"1106","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.045771428,42.3370219500001]},"properties":{"name":"Music Hall Center","owner":"Music Hall Center","address":"350 Madison","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035181","establishmentid":"1106","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/7/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3925","name":"La Casa De La Habana Detroit","address":"1502 Randolph","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"322","name":"Twentieth Century Club, (Gem Theatre)","address":"333 Madison","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4317","name":"Colors","address":"311 E Grand River Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4106","name":"Detroit Seafood Market","address":"1435 Randolph","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5132","name":"Vertical Detroit","address":"1538 Centre St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4844","name":"Centre Park Restaurant","address":"1407 Randolph","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"355","name":"Detroit Athletic Club","address":"241 Madison Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1681","name":"Hilton Garden Inn/ American Grill","address":"351 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4906","name":"Jose's Tacos, LLC","address":"218 E Grand River","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"2048","name":"Elwood Bar & Grill","address":"300 E Adams","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44169","inspectionDate":"2018-11-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Ice bin","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"and the KITCHEN","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"40567","inspectionDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the PESTS","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the base of the Labels","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"36820","inspectionDate":"2016-10-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Utensil(s) and equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned every","subProblem":"","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate sanitary hand drying aids/devices."},{"violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing lavatories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.18","violationDescription":"Except for areas used only for the loading of water or the discharge of SEWAGE and other liquid waste, through the use of a closed system of hoses, SERVICING AREAS shall be provided with overhead protection. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outdoor mobile servicing area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without overhead protection","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide overhead protection."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1106"}}